{"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The French word for glass is glace;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The word news originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The bikini is named after the Bikini Atoll, an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Coca-Cola original colour was green.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}]}
